Finding aid for the Henry Clay Frick Papers, Series II: Correspondence, 1882-1929, undated HCFF.1.2
The Frick Collection/Frick Art Reference Library Archives
- Parsons, John - Patterson, John (Box 72, Folder 5)
  Patterson, Hannah Louise H., 1912
  Patterson, John M., 1892
- Patterson, Paul - Pearson (Box 72, Folder 6)
  Patterson, Paul, 1907
  Patterson, Sterrett and Acheson (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1906
  Patterson, T.C., 1867, 1911
  Patterson, Wm. J., 1917
  Patterson, William Morrison, 1914
  Patton, K., 1908
  Patton, William A., 1908-1910
  Paull, Jas. L., 1890
  Paull, Robert G., 1900
  Pavey, Darwin C., 1900
  Payne, George Henry, 1917, 1919
  Payne, H.C., 1902
  Pazzoli, Sylvio, 1914
  Peabody, F.S., 1902
  Peabody, George L., 1909
  Peabody, Stephen, 1905
  Pearson, F.S., 1914
  Pearson, Henry C., 1900
  Pearson, I., Mrs., 1903
- Pearson's - Pell (Box 72, Folder 7)
  Pearson's Magazine[no place], 1907
  Peary, Robert E., 1908
  Peary Testimonial (National Testimonial to Commander Robert E. Peary), 1910
  Pechstein, Geo. A., 1912
  Pedder, Chas. J., 1902-1903
  Peebles, Maud V. (Mrs. Thomas Chalmers Peebles), 1915
  Peek, Wm. A., 1914
  Peirce, Harold, 1903-1922
  Peirce, John, 1902
  Peixotto, M. Percy, 1902
  Pell, S. Osgood, 1904-1912
- Pen - Pennsylvania National Guard (Box 72, Folder 8)
  Pen and Pencil Club (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1904
  Pence, Sarah E., 1901
  Pendleton, Elizabeth (Mrs. F.K. Pendleton), 1915
  Peninsular Car Co. (Detroit, Mich.), 1887
  Penn, Harvey, 1899-1902
  Penn, W.F., 1901
  Penn Mutual Life Insurance Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1909
  Pennington, J., 1915
  Pennock, Sophia B., 1915
  Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1900
  Pennsylvania Association for the Blind [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1918
  Pennsylvania Child Labor Committee [no place], 1906
  Pennsylvania Children's Home Society (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901
  Pennsylvania College for Women [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1905, 1912
  Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, Department of State Police, 1917
  Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, Department of the Auditor General, 1899
  Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, Executive Chamber, 1904, 1906
  Pennsylvania Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1906
  Pennsylvania Door and Sash Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1905
  Pennsylvania Historical Publishing Association (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1905
  Pennsylvania Lines West of Pittsburgh (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1904, 1908
  Pennsylvania National Bank of Pittsburgh (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1890
  Pennsylvania National Guard, Company F, 14th Regiment, 1907
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1887-1917 (Box 72, Folder 9-11)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company (continued), 1918-1924 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Department - Pennypacker (Box 73, Folder 2)
  Pennsylvania Railroad Department Young Men's Christian Association (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1908-1910
  Pennsylvania Society (New York, N.Y.), 1900-1917
  Pennsylvania Society of Sons of the Revolution (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1900
  Pennsylvania State College (State College, Pa.), 1900
  Pennsylvania Steel Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1906, 1909
  Pennsylvania System (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1921
  Pennsylvania Water and Power Company (New York, N.Y.), 1910-1912
  Pennypacker, S.W., 1914
- Penrose, Boies, 1904-1919 (Box 73, Folder 3-4)
- Peoples - Perkins George W. (Box 73, Folder 5)
  Peoples National Bank of Pittsburgh (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1913
  Peoples Natural Gas Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901, 1921
  People's Symphony Concerts (New York, N.Y.), 1907-1914
  People's University Extension Society of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1908
  Pepper, George, 1919
  Pere Marquette Railroad Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901
  Peregrino, F.Z.S., 1894
  Pereles, T.J., 1905
  Perham, Clara L., 1919
  Perigny, Viscount de, 1910
  Perine, William D.N., 1909
  Perkins, C. Lawrence, 1908
  Perkins Electric Lamp Co. (Boston, Mass.), 1892
  Perkins, George W., 1902-1908
- Perkins, George W. (continued), 1909-1919 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Permanent - Philadelphia and Reading Coal (Box 73, Folder 7)
  Permanent Blind Relief War Fund for Soldiers and Sailors (New York, N.Y.), 1916
  Perrault, J.P., 1905
  Perry, J.M., 1903
  Perry, R. Hinton, 1916
  Perry, W.H., 1892
  Peter, Le Baron Michel, 1917
  Peter Wright and Sons (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1890
  Peters, Ralph, 1909-1916
  Peters, William F., 1915
  Peterson, J.C., 1890
  Petre, M.W., 1898
  Petrie, [?],1906
  Pfaelzer, Franklin T., 1905
  Pfaelzer, Walker and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1904
  Pfahler, Margaret D., 1917
  Pfizer, G.A., 1913
  Pflederer, Dan L., 1916
  Pfohl, W., 1919
  Phelps, E.E., 1919
  Philadelphia and Reading Coal and Iron Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1904, 1915
- Philadelphia and Reading Railway - Philip (Box 73, Folder 8)
  Philadelphia and Reading Railway Co. [various locations], 1904-1915
  Philadelphia Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1886-1921
  Philadelphia Item(Philadelphia, Pa.), 1911
  Philadelphia National Bank (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1903
  Philadelphia Press(Philadelphia, Pa.), 1914
  Philadelphia Securities (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1893
  Philip, J. Van Ness, 1919
- Phillips - Phipps, Annie (Box 73, Folder 9)
  Phillips Academy (Andover, Mass.), 1908
  Phillips and MacConnal (Liverpool, England), 1912, 1919
  Phillips, Charles S., 1900-1917
  Phillips, Francis C., 1897-1898
  Phillips, H.A., 1906, 1910
  Phillips, Harriet Duff (Mrs. John M. Phillips), 1916, 1919
  Phillips, James A., 1891
  Phillips, M.E., 1915
  Phillips property [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1909
  Phillips's (London, England), 1898
  Phillis, Minora F., 1900
  Philp, C. von, 1899
  Phipps, Annie (Mrs. Henry Phipps), 1916
- Phipps, Henry, 1887-1914 (Box 73, Folder 10-11)
- Phipps, John S. ("Jay"), 1901-1919 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Phipps, L.C., 1896-1900 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Pickands, Mather and Co. (Cleveland, Ohio), 1886-1915 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Pickett - Pisor (Box 74, Folder 3)
  Pickett, William L., 1912
  Pictorial News Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1915
  Pier, Arthur Stanwood, 1915
  Pierce, A.M., 1900
  Pierce and Cox (Boston, Mass.), 1902
  Pierce, H.C., 1902
  Pierce, Kelly and Co. (Sharpsville, Pa.), 1890
  Pierce, James B., 1890-1915
  Pierce, Roger, 1914
  Pierce, W.T., 1905
  Pierson, [?], no year
  Pierson U-Bar Company [no place], 1909
  Pigott, H. Herbert, 1898-1899
  Pike, W.L., 1906
  Pilots' Association (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1900
  Pingree, David, 1911
  Pingree, Harriet E., 1911
  Pinkerton's National Detective Agency [various locations], 1886-1906
  Pinkerton, S.S., 1900
  Pinnock, [?],1885
  Pintefract, J.G., 1886, 1894
  Pirie, Fred A., 1921-1922
  Pisor, J.H., 1906
- Pitcairn - Pittsburgh and Allegheny (Box 74, Folder 4)
  Pitcairn, Edward, 1909
  Pitcairn, John, 1897-1909, undated
  Pitcairn, Raymond, 1916
  Pitcairn, Robert, circa 1890, 1891-1910
  Pitney, J.O.H., 1915
  Pitt and Scott [various locations], 1901
  Pittsburgh and Allegheny Free Kindergarten Association (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901, 1906
  Pittsburgh and Allegheny Home for the Friendless (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1921
  Pittsburgh and Allegheny Infants Milk Association (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901
  Pittsburgh and Allegheny Milk and Ice Association (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1909, 1911
- Pittsburgh and Connellsville - Pittsburgh, Cincinnati (Box 74, Folder 5)
  Pittsburgh and Connellsville Gas, Coal and Coke Co. (Connellsville, Pa.), 1888
  Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1886-1903
  Pittsburgh Association for the Improvement of the Poor (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1893-1911
  Pittsburgh Athletic Association (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1908, 1910
  Pittsburgh, Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900-1901
  Pittsburgh-Buffalo Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1913
  Pittsburgh Bulletin (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1906-1917
  Pittsburgh Catholic Lyceum [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1909
  Pittsburgh Chronicle and Telegraph [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1919
  Pittsburgh, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1897-1920
- Pittsburgh Civic - Pittsburgh Evangelistic (Box 74, Folder 6)
  Pittsburgh Civic Commission (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1909-1911
  Pittsburgh Clearing House (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902
  Pittsburgh Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1891-1919
  Pittsburgh Coal Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902-1916
  Pittsburgh Dispatch(Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1906-1911
  Pittsburgh Evangelistic Committee [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1913
- Pittsburgh Field - Pittsburgh Hospital (Box 74, Folder 7)
  Pittsburgh Field Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903-1916
  Pittsburgh Free Dispensary (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1904
  Pittsburgh Fresh Air Fund [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1890
  Pittsburgh Gazette Times[formerly Pittsburgh Gazette] (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1904-1911
  Pittsburgh Golf Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902-1914
  Pittsburgh Grand Opera (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1899
  Pittsburgh-Hickson Co. [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1918
  Pittsburgh Hospital [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1906
  Pittsburgh Hospital for Children (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901, 1906
- Pittsburgh Hotels - Pittsburgh Orchestra (Box 74, Folder 8)
  Pittsburgh Hotels Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1916-1923
  Pittsburgh Hunt Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902
  Pittsburgh Leader(Pittsburgh, Pa.), circa 1900, 1901-1917
  Pittsburgh, McKeesport and Westmoreland Railway Co. [no place], 1910
  Pittsburgh, McKeesport and Youghiogheny Railroad Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1886
  Pittsburgh National Bank of Commerce [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1902
  Pittsburgh Natatorium (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1884-1906, undated
  Pittsburgh Newsboys' Home (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1908-1920
  Pittsburgh Orchestra (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1899-1908
  Pittsburgh Orchestra Association [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1916
- Pittsburgh (Pa.) - Pittsburgh Plate (Box 74, Folder 9)
  Pittsburgh, Pa., Board for the Assessment and Revision of Taxes, 1906
  Pittsburgh, Pa., Board of Assessors' Office, 1888-1889
  Pittsburgh, Pa., Board of Public Education, 1913
  Pittsburgh, Pa., Board of Registration Commissioners, 1908, 1911
  Pittsburgh, Pa., City Treasurer's Office, 1887, 1900
  Pittsburgh, Pa., Department of Public Safety, 1906, 1909
  Pittsburgh, Pa., Department of Public Works, 1898
  Pittsburgh, Pa., Fire Department, 1917
  Pittsburgh, Pa., Port of Pittsburgh Custom-House, 1898
  Pittsburgh, Pa., Post Office, 1902
  Pittsburgh, Pa., Proposed subway, 1919
  Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company, Pittsburgh, Pa., 1901-1922
- Pittsburgh Playground - Pittsburgh Wood (Box 74, Folder 10)
  Pittsburgh Playground Association [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1912
  Pittsburgh Post Office Clerks' Beneficial Association (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903
  Pittsburgh Post[Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1904
  Pittsburgh Press(Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1904
  Pittsburgh Press Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900-1917
  Pittsburgh Screen Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1916
  Pittsburgh Testing Laboratory, Limited (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901
  Pittsburgh Trust Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1893
  Pittsburgh Tube Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1908-1918
  Pittsburgh Typewriter Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1893
  Pittsburgh, Virginia and Charleston Railway Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1891-1901
  Pittsburgh-Westmoreland Coal Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1915
  Pittsburgh Wood Preserving Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1913
- Platt and Woodward, Bankers (New York, N.Y.), 1886-1892 (Box 74, Folder 11-12)
- Playford - Poor's (Box 75, Folder 1)
  Playford, W.H., 1889-1890
  Plaza [Hotel] (New York, N.Y.), 1913
  Plenge, M.K. y Cossío vda. De, 1918
  Plimpton, Geo. A., 1905
  Plotner, W.S., 1897
  Pocahontas Coal and Coke Company [no place], 1918
  Poillon, W.C., 1907, 1913
  Point Judith Polo Club [Point Judith, R.I.], 1910
  Point property [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1902
  Police Pension Fund Association (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1910
  Poling, Martha Black, 1916
  Pollard, A.C., 1891-1892
  Pollard, J.B., 1904
  Pond, Edward H., 1913
  Poor's Railroad Manual Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1912
- Popper and Sternbach, regular account (New York, N.Y.), 1906-1914 (Box 75, Folder 2-10)
- Popper and Sternbach, special account (New York, N.Y.), 1912-1913 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Popper, Edward - Porter, H.H. (Box 76, Folder 2)
  Popper, Edward, 1915
  Porch, Jacob, 1890
  Pore, C.A., 1894
  Porte, James H., 1890
  Porter, Annie de C., undated
  Porter, H.H., 1890-1905
  Porter, H.H., Jr., 1910
- Porter, H.K. - Potter, Chester (Box 76, Folder 3)
  Porter, H.K., 1897-1916
  Porter, Harry, 1914
  Porter, Jas., 1886
  Porter, John Addison [secretary to William McKinley], 1897-1898
  Porter, L.C., 1914
  Porter, Ruth Stephens, 1919
  Post, Harriet (Mrs. William H. Post), 1919
  Post, Henry R., 1896, 1898
  Post, Laura J., 1909
  Postal Telegraph-Cable Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1914-1915
  Potter, Asa P., 1901, 1905
  Potter, Chester D., 1920
  Potter, Chester M., 1918-1919
- Potter, E.C. - Potter, J.A. (Box 76, Folder 4)
  Potter, E.C., 1891-1916
  Potter, Henry Codman, 1907
  Potter, J.A., 1897-1915
- Poud - Pressed (Box 76, Folder 5)
  Poud, Clarence Strong, 1912
  Poughkeepsie Bridge Company [no place], 1892
  Power, C.B., 1889
  Powers, L.M., 1916
  Pratt, Enoch, 1893
  Pratt, John T., 1914
  Pratt, Sereno S., 1909
  Presbyterian Hospital [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1913
  Prescott and Smith, later Prescott and Bidwell (Mitchell, S.D.), 1889, 1893
  "The President" [Theodore Roosevelt], 1907
  Press Association [later Press Association Compilers, Inc.] (New York, N.Y.), 1913-1918
  Press Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1917
  Pressed Radiator Company of America (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1909
- Preston - Pride (Box 76, Folder 6)
  Preston, Alice, 1915
  Preston and Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1897
  Preston, Charles F., 1902
  Preston, James P., 1913
  Preston, Percy, 1896
  Preszburg, R., 1915
  Prevost, S. Mallet, 1890-1908
  Price, B. Lillian S., 1906
  Price, C.S., 1892
  Price, Theo. H., 1906
  Price, Waterhouse and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1910-1915
  Pride, Edwin, 1908
  Pride, Elisha S., 1916
  Pride, Willis A., 1906
- Prince, Abigail - Prince, W.B. (Box 76, Folder 7)
  Prince, Abigail, 1907-1908
  Prince, F.H., 1902-1917
  Prince, George S., 1902
  Prince, Gustave A., 1905
  Prince, Morton, 1907
  Prince O.A., 1909
  Prince, W.B., 1916
- Princeton Alumni - Princeton University (Box 76, Folder 8)
  Princeton Alumni Association of Western Pennsylvania (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1910
  Princeton Bric-a-Brac(Princeton, N.J.), 1901
  Princeton Club of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1916
  Princeton Pictorial Review(Princeton, N.J.), 1915
  Princeton University (Princeton, N.J.), 1912-1916
- Princeton University (continued) - Pritts (Box 76, Folder 9)
  Princeton University, Princeton, N.J., 1917-1924
  Pritchett, Henry S., 1915-1919
  Pritts, M.E., 1901
- Proctor - Puig (Box 76, Folder 10)
  Proctor, A. Phimister, 1902, 1908
  Proctor, E. Pookman, 1889 or 1899
  Proctor, James H., 1908
  Proctor, W. Ross, 1913
  Professional Chauffeurs' Club of America (New York, N.Y.), 1916
  Professional Woman's League, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1916
  Progress Company [no place], 1909
  Promberger, John, 1900
  Property Owners Committee (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1890
  Prosser, L.S., 1898
  Protestant Home for Incurables (Pittsburgh, Pa.), undated
  Proudfoot's Commercial Agency [no place], 1908
  Prowattain, Ivan, 1896-1897
  Prudential Trust Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901-1902
  Prudhomme, L. Narcisse, 1907
  Prussing and Hutchins (Chicago, Ill.), 1889
  Public Ledger(Philadelphia, Pa.), 1916, 1919
  Public Pointer[no place], 1905
  Puffer, Dora, 1901
  Puffer, R.M., Mrs., 1917
  Pugh, C.E., 1890
  Puig, Juan de la C., 1915
- Pugliatti - Pullman Company (Box 76, Folder 11)
  Pugliatti, Thomas P. (Duke of Sangiorgio), 1911, 1914
  Pulling, T.J., 1908
  Pullman Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900-1922
- Pullman Palace - Pyne (Box 77, Folder 1)
  Pullman Palace Car Porters and Railway Employees Beneficial Association (Jersey City, N.J.), 1901-1913
  Pullman Ticket Office, Boston and Maine Railroad (Boston, Mass.), 1920
  Pullman's Palace Car Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1891-1899
  Punch and Judy Theatre (New York, N.Y.), 1915
  Putnam's Monthly[no place], 1908
  Pyne, M. Taylor, 1914-1918
  Pyne, Percy R., II, 1915
  Quay, Elizabeth W. (Mrs. R.R. Quay), 1900, undated
- Quay, M.S., 1888-1903 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Quay, R.R.- Rainey (Box 77, Folder 3)
  Quay, R.R., 1899-1914
  Queen, Emmet, 1906
  Quill, James J., 1912
  Quinby, Charles T., 1915
  R. and J. Farquhar and Co. (Boston, Mass.), 1912
  R.G. Dun and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1891
  R.H. Goodell and Co. [no place], 1909
  R.J. Horner and Co. (New York, N.Y.), no year
  R.L. Polk and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1915
  R.P. Flower and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1890
  Rabourdin, E., 1913
  Racquet and Tennis Club (New York, N.Y.), 1905-1917
  Radford, Jones and Co. (London, England), no year
  Rafferty, A.F., 1911
  Rafferty, B.F., 1890
  Rafferty, G.T., 1888, 1896
  Railway Investors' League [no place], 1916
  Railway World(Philadelphia, Pa.), 1904
  Rainey, W.J., 1887-1898
- Raisig - Ramsay, Erskine (Box 77, Folder 4)
  Raisig, Chas., 1901-1902
  Ralphsnyder, George M., 1914
  Ralston, B.S. (Duquesne Greys, Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903
  Ramsay, Adelaide Frick, 1910
  Ramsay, Erskine, 1896-1919
- Ramsay, Morris, 1884-1892 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Ramsay, Robert, 1886-1898 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Ramsay, William - Ramsey (Box 77, Folder 7)
  Ramsay, William, 1896-1912
  Ramsey, A.C., Mrs., 1899
  Ramsey, W.W., 1898, 1901
- Randall, E.E., 1920-1921 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Randle - Raymond (Box 77, Folder 9)
  Randle, William G., 1901
  Randolph and McClements, Florists (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900, 1909
  Ranke, Marie L., 1915
  Rankin, Henry Irwin, 1905
  Rankin, J., 1911
  Raphael, Sr., 1900
  Rasin, Mifflin, 1905
  Rassett, Florence, 1907
  Ratcliffe, Minnie, 1912-1913, no year
  Rath-Merrill, Mary E., 1911
  Rauh, Bertha F. (Mrs. Enoch Rauh), 1904-1911
  Ravenscroft, W.S., 1886
  Ray, Frank W., 1908, 1910
  Ray, J.M., 1899
  Raymond, G.H., 1891
  Raymond, Jerome H., 1898
  Raymond, John W., 1904
- Rea Bros. - Rea, Samuel (Box 77, Folder 10)
  Rea Bros. and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1887-1892
  Rea, C.S., 1898, 1916
  Rea, Henry R., 1916
  Rea, James C., 1901, 1911
  Rea, Samuel, 1889-1906
- Rea, Samuel (continued), 1907-1913 (Box 77, Folder 11-12)
- Rea, Samuel (continued), 1913-1920 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Read - Real Estate Exchange (Box 78, Folder 2)
  Read, James Charles, 1914
  Reading Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1904-1920
  Reading Hardware Company (Reading, Pa.), 1901
  Reagan, James, 1891
  Reagan, James W., 1913
  Real Estate Company of Pittsburgh (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1916
  Real Estate Exchange (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1915
- Real Estate Trust Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900-1919 (Box 78, Folder 3-4)
- Realty - Reed, James A. (Box 78, Folder 5)
  Realty Trust Co. (Youngstown, Ohio), 1904-1905
  Ream, Norman B., 1899-1917
  Ream, Robert C., 1907-1914
  Reath, Theodore W., 1918
  Reay, R. Martine, 1916
  Recess (New York, N.Y.), 1911-1921
  Records of the Past Exploration Society (Washington, D.C.), 1904
  Red Cross Christmas Seals (New York, N.Y.), 1916
  Redfield, William C., 1917
  Redpath-Brockway Chautauqua Society (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1916
  Reed and Wilkins (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1922
  Reed B. Coyle and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1895, 1898
  Reed, Blanche H. (Mrs. W.S. Reed), 1906
  Reed, Chester D., 1900
  Reed, J. Sanders, 1903
  Reed, James A., 1919
- Reed, James H., 1889-1913 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Reed, John - Reid, Daniel (Box 78, Folder 7)
  Reed, John B., Jr., 1891
  Reed, Joseph P., 1898
  Reed, Smith, Shaw and Beal (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1914, 1922
  Reed, Smith, Shaw and McClay (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1922
  Reed, T.B., 1896-1897
  Rees, Will T., 1902
  Reese, Cara, 1900
  Regan, M.J., 1909, 1911
  Reggio, A. Nicholas, 1913
  Reha, M.J., Mrs., 1923
  Reichlin, Edward A., 1912-1914
  Reid, Daniel G., 1902-1918
- Reid, Elizabeth - Republican (Box 78, Folder 8)
  Reid, Elizabeth Sturges, 1905
  Reid, J.B., 1915
  Reid, Mae G., 1920
  Reid, Whitelaw, 1910
  Reiff, W.E., 1903
  Reimer, A.F., 1911-1916
  Reineman, Robert T., 1913
  Reinemer, C., 1914
  Reinhart, J.Mc.H., 1895-1903
  Reinhardt, O.E., 1903
  Reinhardt, R.F., 1900
  Reis, W.E., 1899
  Reisner, George A., 1911-1912
  Rembrandt Club of Brooklyn [Brooklyn, N.Y.], 1916
  Rembrandt painting, 1912
  Renault Freres Agency, Inc. [no place], 1905
  Rend, W.P., 1905
  Reno, Elizabeth B., 1915
  Renshaw, Maida B. (Mrs. Clarence Renshaw), 1918
  Reppert, E.H., 1890-1915
  Republic Iron and Steel Company [no place], 1904
  Republican Club of the 15th Assembly District [New York, N.Y.], 1919
  Republican Club of the City of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1919
  Republican National Committee [no place], 1904-1919
  Republican State Committee (New York, N.Y.), 1906-1912
- Resler - Rice (Box 78, Folder 9)
  Resler, Ed. D., 1897
  Retter, Carl, 1891
  Reuling, Geo., 1903, 1913
  Revay, G., 1903
  Revillon Freres (New York, N.Y.), 1902
  Rex, Alfred C., 1918
  Rex Carbon Coal Co. [no place], 1911
  Rex Mining Company (Spokane, Wash.), 1907
  Reymer and Brothers (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902
  Reynolds, D.R., 1906
  Reynolds, David, 1918
  Reynolds, Eliza B., 1900-1910
  Reynolds, F.M., 1887
  Reynolds, Frank, 1915
  Reynolds, Harris A., 1912
  Reynolds, Henry E., 1911
  Reynolds, John Phillips, 1906, 1912
  Reynolds, Marion J., 1900
  Reynolds painting, 1913
  Reynolds, William T., 1909, 1911
  Rhind, J. Massey, 1917-1918
  Rhodes, Wm., 1888
  Rhule, Geo. M., 1910
  Rial, John, 1896
  Rice, Blanche P., 1920
  Rice, J. Lewis, 1909
  Rice, Joseph, Mrs., 1891, 1894
- Rich - Rico (Box 78, Folder 10)
  Rich, Charles C., Mrs., 1916
  Richard, L.B., 1905
  Richard Irvin and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1900
  Richards, A.F., Mrs., 1912
  Richards, Guy, 1902
  Richards, Jos. T., 1897
  Richards, W.G., 1906
  Richardson, Harriet T., 1907
  Richardson, W.C., 1899
  Richardson, W.T., 1891
  Richey, E.O. (Lizzie O. Richey), 1904-1909
  Richey, Muriel, 1901-1902
  Richmond-Eureka Mining Co. (Portland, Me.), 1906-1922
  Ricker, V.C., 1919
  Rickey, J.K., 1900
  Rico, Martin, 1907
- Riddell - Ringwalt (Box 78, Folder 11)
  Riddell, Laura Grace, 1900
  Rider, Jos. G., 1898-1899
  Ridgely, M.G., 1910
  Riding Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900
  Riding Club (New York, N.Y.), 1905-1909
  Rigas, S.S., 1913
  Riggs, C.W., 1892
  Riggs, Francis B., 1904, 1916
  Riker, Ella C. (Mrs. A.P. Riker), 1912
  Riley, Don, 1899-1900
  Riley, Frank J., 1915
  Riley, James, 1902-1909
  Riley, Walter J., 1923-1924
  Rinehart, J.B.F., 1901-1902
  Ring, J.E., 1894
  Ring, John F., 1923
  Ringwalt, H.L., 1901-1910
- Ripley, E.P., 1905-1919 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Rist - Ritz (Box 79, Folder 2)
  Rist, Benjamin, 1896, 1901
  Rist, J.J., 1891-1892
  Rist, Mary F., 1898-1909
  Rist, Peter, 1891
  Rist, Sarah, 1896-1909
  Ristigouche Salmon Club (Matapedia, Canada), 1909-1916
  Ritchie, C.S., 1893
  Rittenberry, Alma, 1915
  Ritter, Alexander, 1911
  Ritter, P., 1914
  Ritz-Carlton Hotel (New York, N.Y.), 1912
- Riverside - Roberts, Percival (Box 79, Folder 3)
  Riverside Iron Works (Wheeling, W.Va.), 1891
  Robb, Geo., 1908
  Robbins, A.M., 1891, 1897
  Robbins, Edward E., 1889-1911
  Robbins, Francis L., 1891-1903
  Robbins, K.W., 1899
  Robbins, Reginald C., 1912
  Robbins, T.E., 1889
  Robbins, W.D., 1917
  Rob[er]t Fulton Monument Association [no place], 1909
  Rob[er]t Glendinning and Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1890
  Roberts, Alice B., 1912
  Roberts and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1902
  Roberts, Ellen D., 1911-1912
  Roberts, G.B., 1890-1891
  Roberts, Percival, Jr., 1915
- Roberts, W. - Robinson, Anna (Box 79, Folder 4)
  Roberts, W., 1910-1919
  Roberts, W.A., 1908
  Robertson, Robert, 1902
  Robins, Wm., 1901
  Robinson and Orr (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1909
  Robinson, Anna L., 1902
- Robinson Brothers, Bankers and Brokers (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1888-1910 (Box 79, Folder 5-6)
- Robinson, C.L.F. - Robinson, John (Box 79, Folder 7)
  Robinson, C.L.F., 1909
  Robinson, D.S., 1903
  Robinson, Douglas, 1905-1914
  Robinson, Edward, 1906-1914
  Robinson, Fred'k. O., 1911
  Robinson, G.B., Mrs., 1900
  Robinson, George M., 1906
  Robinson, H.L., 1889
  Robinson, H.R., Mrs., 1914